A Guide to the Records of the Staff Association of the University of Virginia Library, 1982-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Records of the Staff Association of the University of Virginia Library 1982-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG 12/25/1.991
This collection consists of ca. 1,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These papers were transferred from the Library Staff Association through Christina Deane, Government Information Resources, Alderman Library on July 14, 1999.
Scope and Content Information
Records of the Library Staff Association, ca. 1966, 1971-1997, ca. 1,000 items (4 Hollinger boxes) consists of bylaws, bank statements and financial receipts, constitutions, computer disks, correspondence, membership lists, minutes, photographs, thank-you cards, notebooks, and miscellaneous material. Topics include the annual Christmas Party, field trips, memorial contributions, and the installation of a snack machine.
Contents List
- Acknowledgments and Greeting Cards 1983-1997 (Box 1)
- Bank Statements and Tax Forms (2 folders) 1983-1992 (Box 1)
- Staff Association Christmas Party 1982-1990 (Box 1)
- Staff Association Constitution and Bylaws ca. 1966-1988 (Box 1)
- Staff Association Documents Printed from Disks ca. 1988-1992 (Box 1)
- Staff Association Field Trips (3 folders) 1985-1990 (Box 2)
- Staff Association Memorial Contribution Records 1984-1991 (Box 2)
- Staff Association Notebook (4 folders) ca. 1986-1998 (Box 2)
- Staff Association Notebook ca. 1987-1996 (Box 3)
- Staff Association Papers (5 folders) 1971-1988 (Box 3)
- Staff Association Papers (5 folders) 1989-1991, 1995-1998 (Box 4)
- Staff Association Photographs n.d. (Box 4)
- Staff Association Signs (Drafts) n.d. (Box 4)
- Staff Association Snack Machine Questionnaires and Correspondence 1988 (Box 4)